Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying roads drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
And thus a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting,
hey, there will not feel it alive,
look out below, wake up sunshine,
here we go.
Raise your flag up high,
hail a brand new dawn.
Blaze across the sky, time
to journey on, on your mark.
Come aboard with me.
We're on Earth a legendary.
If you can show your breath.
Then we'll make some waves.
We run our daunted.
Ain't no beginners.
Cause if you're wanted.
Then you're a winner.
For we are on the cruise.
And freedom is the only rule.
Fearless night and day.
Cause that's just our way.
Find one piece.
I'll be the first.
I've heard it be so bad just at first.
It's all this real.
It must be cause my hand's on the wheel.
I'm done playing, feel it's waiting.
In the world I'm feeling alive.
But I'll be loud.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go.
We have come so far.
Gotta make it to the end.
Whatever danger we find,
no one ever left behind.
I've always got your back, my friend.
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward.
Dreaming from the very
first day I'd make my name.
And don't you know that
dream hasn't changed.
I'm done playing through with the wave.
In the world I'm feeling
alive, look out below.
Wake up, sunshine.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
We go!
Oh, yummy!
Baratsumi!
Is there anything you're
neglecting to tell me?
Have you received a reply from
Princess Shirahoshi yet? No!
Sorry, Captain Deccan!
There's still no work!
Just how long has she kept me waiting?
Uh, about ten years or so.
She's really taking her time.
I don't blame her.
This is the doing of
that despicable Neptune.
He intends to force the princess
into a political marriage.
Or so I suspect.
Ten years now!
That heartless monarch
has kept his daughter
locked in a steel tower
for an entire decade!
Oh, how it pains me so!
This cruel tragedy!
The princess and I are in love! Ha!
So, I suspect,
no matter how far I search
along this vast sea floor,
I will never find another as big
and beautiful as you, my dear.
We are meant to be together. Yes.
And so,
I'll twist the head of fate itself to
prevent you from being with anyone else.
I'd rather see you dead.
Your choice.
You can live as my wife
or stop living altogether.
Let me give you another token of my love.
An axe with a rose on it.
Accept this emblem of my
deadly and dying love.
Captain, isn't that the wrong direction?
Don't be a fool!
You know I never miss my target!
Just watch.
In reverse course!
And look, it's heading straight
towards the rear new palace!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Calm down!
It's a hungry pirate looking
for something to eat!
Jeez, listen to me!
Hey!
She's so loud!
My ears!
Princess Hero, she's crying!
Get to the hard shell tower!
Fine, but where the hell
are the on-duty guards?
What?
So there's nobody protecting her?
I'm sorry, sir!
The guards are in the
middle of changing shifts!
No excuses! To the tower!
Somebody help me!
Please!
There's a human here in my chambers!
A bloodthirsty human aiming
to kill me, I'm certain!
Huh? No! Hey!
Go make this stuff up!
I just wanted that food!
I didn't even know you
were in here, all right?
What was that?
Who's throwing axes?
What's all that noise?
Sorry.
Is everything all right, princess?
Are you injured somehow?
Um, I'm fine.
You were crying even louder than usual.
It gave us quite the fright.
Hey, pull me down!
Hold on, the door was already open.
Did you see any intruders here, princess?
Perhaps a strong current opened it.
I woke crying from a
bad dream, that's all.
I swear I just heard someone.
Oh, are you certain?
Ah, that reminds me.
I have some rather dire and vexing
information I must relay to you immediately.
Yeah, it's regarding the pirate who saved
megalo the one known as Straw Hat luffy.
Some mermaid girls were kidnapped
and he's our prime suspect.
Also, based on a troubling
prediction from madam charlie,
the Straw Hat crew is considered a
potential risk for the entire kingdom.
So we've locked them in the
palace prison just to be safe.
We already have the swordsman in custody.
Upon arrival, he drank himself
into a state of compliance.
Three other members of the
crew have? just arrived.
And I imagine they're in
custody as well by now.
But their captain,
well, he might be more perceptive than he
appears and picked up on our intentions,
for he seems to
have fled.
He is almost certainly hiding somewhere
in the palace, so please be careful.
We'll catch the rest of them
on the island in no time.
I can promise you that.
We will defend
this country as well as
your home at any cost.
Well, what I wanted to
say, I feel awful that
we have to arrest the
people who saved Megalow.
I know how much he means to you.
Five minutes
already?
Well, we'll be going now.
You saved me.
Thank you so much.
I'm sorry.
I should have given you a chance earlier.
I hope you'll forgive me if I
had only known who you were,
That you were the one who saved
Megalo Not to be overly familiar,
but may I call you Luffy?
Yeah, sure So, Luffy, they said
that you're a pirate, right?
Does that mean you're a bad person?
I don't know.
I think I'll let you make that call. Okay.
Oh, I don't know if you just heard.
But our soldiers have taken
your friends into custody.
Yeah, that's no big deal.
Trust me on this.
There's no way your guys can
keep them locked up for long.
Really? Huh. Yeah.
Don't worry about it, though.
So, what's with the axe? Let me hear it.
You know who threw the thing?
Were they trying to hit you?
I know who threw it.
And yes, he was.
His name is Vander
Decken, and he's a pirate.
He wanted to marry me, and I refused.
So he wants to kill me now.
And he will.
There's no escape.
You see he ate the mark mark
fruit and he used that power to
mark me all he has to do is
throw a weapon and it will find
me that's why I never leave
here my only real chance to
continue living is being locked
away inside the hardshell tower
So this creep wants to
marry you but he's trying
to kill you yes I've
been in here 10 years.
10 whole years?
Man, you must be bored. Indeed.
And my father made a well-meaning
but misguided rule.
So now, no one can visit
for more than 5 minutes.
Which is why, Megalo's
my only real friend.
Without him, well, I wouldn't
have anyone to talk to. Yeah,
they were gonna Throw
a big banquet to thank
us for saving him that's
been cancelled now.
Or maybe they were just worried you would
consume the entire kingdom's food supply?
You humans sure do eat a lot despite how
small you are that's the old guy's fault.
He made a big fuss about the banquet
when then he kept getting yelled at.
I finally couldn't wait any longer,
so I followed the smell here.
Hey, by the way, did they
call you princess? Yes.
So you're the mermaid princess? Yes.
That does come with being
King Neptune's daughter.
My name is Shirahoshi.
Shirahoshi.
That's too tough to say.
Ooh, I'm eating that.
You know, I could be wrong, but you
haven't struck me as a bad person so far.
Are you an adventurer?
Is that why you decided
to become a pirate?
How wonderful!
Then you must have seen the sun
many times in your adventures.
Oh yeah, and what do the stars
in the night sky look like?
Oh, I bet you've seen
all sorts of animals.
And flowers too, huh?
Now what else? Oh, right.
Have you ever been to the green place?
I think perhaps people call it a forest.
Hey, relax.
You ask too many questions.
Give me a sec.
It's cute how full your cheeks are.
Stop it!
What the heck is wrong with you?
Please don't.
Please don't yell at me.
I just can't handle it.
Oh, no.
You're such a... brute.
Whoa, calm down.
This is nothing to cry over.
Stop.
No one has ever yelled at me before,
and I don't like it. It's horrible.
How can someone so big be
such a coward and a crybaby?
You know, I don't think I like you.
How could you say that?
No one's ever said such
an awful thing to me!
You're such a terrible man!
Please, just go, I want you to leave!
I can't take it!
It hurts too much!
I am full!
Thanks for the grub!
With as long as you've been stuck in here,
no wonder you're scared of everything!
Leave, Luffy!
Just please get out of here!
I could, but isn't there some
place that you want to go?
Well, of course there is.
There are lots of places
that I'd love to see. Why?
Thought you'd say that.
So, let's get out of here. What?
Let's go take a stroll. No!
You're not supposed to!
I can't do that! Why not?
Just do it!
You'll be okay.
If that guy throws something at you, fine.
I'll take it down just like the last time.
Who's up, Chin? Nani-Chin? Brooke-Chin?
Apprehend them now!
They're just three, me three, humans!
Don't do anything dumb!
Please, you've got to stop resisting!
You really will be
criminals if you don't! Yet.
There is no just cause
for them to lock us up.
Sorry, Kuma.
This is such a total letdown.
I really wanted that banquet.
At this point, playing
nice won't do much good.
You heard what he said.
They've made up their minds
about what kind of people we are.
If they desire, we'll stay and
fight them till the end of time.
Surely the three of
them aren't that strong.
They must be bluffing. Listen up.
No one knows what the future holds.
So whether we're heroes or villains,
you still shouldn't cross us.
Is it me, or has he really
gotten his act together? See?
This is a very prologue to the
future that's been foreseen.
Then it's your fault.
We wouldn't have fought back in the first
place if you guys didn't
insist on fighting us.
Hmm, good point. Ha!
But this is nothing.
Not compared to the giant
insect attack I went
through back when I was
on the Bowen Islands.
Behold!
My new weapon, Black Cabotol! Ha!
I'm happy to give you a demonstration.
Please keep that tune!
We need your help!
Is it really fair to
arrest someone based on
a prediction that they
will commit a crime?
I need time to contemplate this.
It's a precarious situation.
And until I decide, you will
have to wait in custody!
Please fight for a minute!
I thought they locked you up!
Sounded like you guys were
having some fun, so...
Here I am.
Just wait for me there, Waratsumi. Sure!
I know it, Captain!
Red Deacon's here!
I knew he'd come!
Welcome sorry to keep
you gentlemen waiting we
ran into a bit of a
volcanic eruption a pity.
And you must be the notorious 40 i
suspect enough flattery you're notorious.
We both are.
Naughty Vanderdecken.
Pleasure to meet you.
A formal handshake.
Just a moment.
That's a bit tricky for a fellow like me.
There we go.
Never mind.
Nice to meet you too.
It's a pleasure.
Mr.
Heart Jones
Nothing on the seafloor can stop us now.
The worst of the worst together, at last!
King Neptune is a royal nuisance,
for you and I alike, I'm sure.
Oh yeah, we got the same goal here.
His army, they take no
pride in being fishmen.
So together, we will conquer them.
And then we kill Neptune, god of the sea.
And lastly, we will destroy
the entire Ryugu kingdom!
Oh no!
What have you guys done?
Yeah, this is overkill!
They're not bad guys!
We were just doing their jobs!
You didn't have to be so rough!
In case you forgot, it was you
guys who started this fight!
All I did was save you idiots!
We would have been fine if we just
acted tough and then ran for it!
To think I gave up sightseeing and
shopping on the island to come here.
What's the point of even
complaining about it anyway?
Not like we could take it back!
The point is, it shouldn't have happened!
We look like villains now!
No one's gonna believe
we took a trip to Fishman
Island and just happened
to seize their palace!
Would you prefer we let
ourselves get captured?
I'd prefer if we'd gone with
my runaway plan, like I said!
Which wouldn't have worked,
because I don't know how to get out
of here, and Luffy's still missing!
That's a really good point
that I hadn't thought about!
Any idea where Luffy went? No.
We really have to go, so could
you help us out, pretty please?
Maybe he can tell you where to find Luffy.
Tell me where I can
find the treasure vault.
Cut it out!
Who, me?
Don't play innocent with me!
You think I don't know how
your greedy brain works?
All right, everybody, let's take a little
break and turn those frowns upside down.
With rock!
It'll be all right, no reason to fight.
Words of mine aren't lies, everybody dies.
You are helping the situation, So King!
Are you feeling any
better now, your highness?
I can't believe that even the great knight
of the sea was bested by these mongrels.
Things would have been different if I
hadn't thrown my back out all of a sudden.
I don't know when I became so old.
This is all my fault.
Forgive me.
Don't say that, your highness.
If we had gathered our wits sooner,
we could have burst their
bubbles and won easily.
Now that they've drained the water
from the room, it's hopeless.
And who will rescue us now?
Hey, you criminals!
It's only a matter of time
before Neptune's sons Fukaboshi,
Ryoboshi, and Manboshi
return to the palace.
And once they get here,
you're all going to be sorry.
Yo-ho-ho-ho! Yeah!
Doesn't matter who's coming, we
have to make it off this island.
Our first step should be
getting everyone together.
Then we find the sunny and
get the hell out of here.
But we lost our coding when we got
here, so even if we knew where it was,
we couldn't escape on it as it is.
To top it all off, the log
pose hasn't been working.
It's been going haywire ever
since we arrived on the island.
You can't be serious.
If you believe a primitive pose like
that will get you through the new world,
then you're even dumber
than you look Wait,
are you trying to say that
my gear isn't good enough?
I'm not saying anything
unless you untie me first.
It must be Prince Fukaboshi.
This is quite unusual.
What could be delaying
the guards from answering?
Who's this?
What do you want?
What are you doing?
Hang up, Prince Fukaboshi!
Help me!
Everybody, shut up!
Prince Ryuboshi!
Prince Maboshi!
Oh no! Something's wrong!
I can hear them call for Merde!
It sounds like they're in trouble,
but I didn't hear Father Shirahoshi!
It's us, the three
princes. What has happened?
With whom am I currently speaking?
Open the gate and grant us passage.
That is an order from the royal family.
Wow, I'm really shaking in my boots here.
Sorry, you're not coming in.
Okay, how about we just hang up?
You don't need to make them angry.
Can you do Kuma and me a favor and tie us
up so we don't look like your accomplices?
Zorochen is scary.
So tell me, are you a member
of the Straw Hat Pirates?
He is, my son.
The man you are speaking to is their
green-haired swordsman, Pirate Hunter Saru.
Zoro!
Wait, that's father.
Is he all right?
Yeah, he's alive.
Well, for now, anyway.
But if you want him and the
others to stay like that,
you're going to have to
run some errands for us.
You can start by getting us
ready to sail out of here.
What that means is finding our ship,
the Sunny, and getting a fresh
new coating slapped on it.
And I mean finding, because we
got no clue where it is right now.
While you're at it, round up our crew.
We're missing a gloomy lady,
a big robot thing,
talking raccoon and a
little goblin pervert and
demands one million berries
and unmarked cash you
stop spurring him on
the goblin isanji that's
hilarious sorrow you are
not helping at all brook
fine i accept your conditions
i will make the proper
arrangements for you and your
friends to leave fishman island you
have my word however i will
dismiss our contract if any of
the hostages are harmed it's
a deal but brother we have no
choice but to agree as you
are aware this gateway is the
only means of entering ryugu
palace even for us of the royal
family while we could try to
gain access from another area
there is simply no way for us to
penetrate the layers of bubbles
there's something i must say before we go
i wouldn't normally share this information
given the circumstances however i am honor
bound to deliver the message regardless
i'm listening they are from the first son
of the sea and former warlord jimbe for
Straw Hat luffy these were meant to be
delivered upon your arrival on the island
as part of your welcoming but here we are
jimbe but why and how do they know jimbe
wait that's right yeah luffy said jimbe
was his friend true the two of them even
appeared together in the newspaper a
while back despite being a pirate jimbe is
almost like a hero to the people down here
unfortunately luffy isn't with us right
at this moment but i'll pass the messages
on go you would have my thanks the first
is do not fight and as
for the second jimbe
will wait in the sea forest that is all
don't fight Heart what does
that even mean have you
heard the rumors going around
the ones about the straw
hat pirates it's crazy
you think they really took
over yugu palace what is it
they're after anyway that
can't be i met them they
seem like such nice people
i can't believe they do
such a thing i bet they did
kidnap those mermaids and
the way things are going it
won't be long before they
come after the rest of us.
Madam Charlie's vision is coming true.
I guess they're finally
showing their true colors.
I heard that two of them have been hiding
around here in the back
of the Mermaid Cafe.
That's why the guards are
inspecting it right now.
It's time for Kong Fu Point.
Sanji's finally recovering.
He needs peace and quiet at any cost.
You want to take us to
the Ryugu Palace, huh?
I don't know what's happening
here, but we're not going.
Hey, Chopper, you okay?
Sanji, you shouldn't be up and about.
Go back to bed. No fighting.
I'm not fighting.
I just want to ask them
something about the Ryugu Palace.
Is she there?
The mermaid princess?
Yeah, she's there. So what? I'll
go. It's worth it. Oh, it isn't?
You're still too weak.
If she's beautiful,
you might die! Come on!
Aren't you ready yet?
Let's get going!
I can't, though I'd like to. Then why not?
You said there was somewhere
you wanted to see, didn't you?
I did, but if I leave my room,
it'll cause a lot of problems.
And not just for me, but for
everyone in the palace, too.
Look, I'm not telling you
how to live your life,
but I'd be going crazy if I was
stuck in one room for ten years.
I'll make sure you're safe.
It's my thanks for all that food!
So, where do you want to go?
The sea.
The sea forest.
Sorry.
I suppose it's a foolish dream.
I could never forgive myself
for doing something so selfish.
Just forget about it.
We're just standing here talking.
What are you apologizing for?
Because I can't stop crying.
Just saying that took all of my courage.
Please don't get angry and
start yelling at me again!
It's really frightening when you do that!
Such a pain in the butt!
Help!
That doesn't sound good! No!
Why now of all times?
Vander Decken must be behind this!
He's attacking the hard shell tower!
Shura Hachi is in danger!
Tell me, how many guards are with her?
Unfortunately, all of the
guards are tied up here, sire.
Listen, pirates.
I need you to go check on the princess.
This is an emergency.
Whoa, we have to do what now?
No, King Deptune.
We can't possibly trust
them with her safety.
I'm afraid there simply
isn't any other choice.
The hard-shell tower is on the
northeast side of the palace.
Please, you have to
hurry there immediately.
Do you not realize that as a hostage,
you don't get to make demands?
Be quiet, you!
Shirahoshi is the only daughter I have!
You may not realize, but her
life is constantly under threat.
If anything should happen to
her while you occupy our home,
I will send you all to your graves
at the bottom of an ocean trance!
Well, how could I possibly
refuse going to her rescue?
I shall rush to her aid in this,
her greatest moment of need!
Completely selflessly, of course!
No hint of an ulterior motive!
Although, if she wanted to show me
her panties, that would be fine.
It might be a trap! No! This is awful!
The only one of them who's willing to
help us has the most impure of intentions.
She's in worse danger now than ever!
Please take me with you!
You don't have to untie me, but I
insist that I accompany you, skeleton!
The tower is my jurisdiction!
If anything happens to the princess, I
will never be able to overcome my shame!
I understand.
You desire.
I'm sorry to burden you, but it truly
is my dream to go to the sea forest.
And these ten years, I couldn't.
Whenever I talk about making the trip,
everyone goes out of their way to tell me
how dangerous it would be for me to leave.
So I've never pushed the
issue because I'm too afraid.
Tell me the truth.
Are you really willing to take me to the
sea forest despite the trouble you'll face?
Yes.
And you promise to protect me
no matter what happens, right?
Of course I will.
Count on me.
Whoa, hold on.
I'm not going to do it if you keep crying.
And if I'm being honest here,
you'll be the one taking me,
since I can't swim and all.
Don't cry, but that'll be
hard, because I'm so happy.
Is there anything that
doesn't make you cry?
Well, anyway, when we
go to leave this place,
everyone's going to
recognize you, aren't they?
Yes, that'll be a problem.
No, it won't, because I've got the
perfect idea to get you out of here.
Mermaid Princess!
Are you alright?
Look over there at the tower.
This is worse than my greatest fear!
Those weren't the sounds of
axes or knives like usual.
What we heard were the bodies of human
pirates slamming against the tower.
How disgusting?
That Vanderdecken, he's
nothing short of a monster.
I think we're in trouble.
I think you're right.
It appears they all survived.
But how?
The Ryugu Palace is
supposed to be impregnable,
yet we've been invaded by enemy forces!
The king, the princess, everyone
here, we're all in danger!
Hey, it sounds like it finally stopped.
You ready, scaredy-cat?
Sure.
We're counting on you, Megalos.
Let's go! Break through!
Megalo!
And Luffy is with him!
We're off to the sea forest!